Fabio T. Hiroki

fabiothiroki@gmail.com +55 11 99477-8245

Summary

Software developer with 3+ years of experience in mobile development. My main focus is in both Android and iOS platforms, in which I have successful published apps. Highly interested in agile development, software quality, process improvement and people management.

Knowledge

OO Programming	Continuous Integration	Mobile Architecture
Design Patterns	Unit Tests	Git
SOLID Principles	NoSQL	Agile Project Management

Work Experience

Taqtile Mobility Project Leader

Jan 2014 - Present

Responsibilities:

- Ensure software quality and deadlines
- Maintain a productive working environment for the team based on agile practices
- Work with the team coding features and fixing bugs

Technologies:

- Android SDK/Java, Cocoa Framework/Objective-C
- NodeJS/ExpressJS, Coffeescript, MongoDB

Taqtile Mobility

Jan 2013 - Dec 2013

Intern

Responsibilities:

• Development and maintenance of native mobile applications for Android and iOS platforms

Technologies:

Android SDK/Java, Cocoa Framework/Objective-C, SQLite

Early Career

Innovatech Telecom

Mar 2011- Mar 2012

Intern

Development of a real-time web-based vehicle tracking system using HTML, CSS, Javascript and Django Framework

C2C Balloon

Feb 2010 - Mar 2011

Intern

Development and maintenance of web applications using HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, MySQL

Education

University of Campinas (UNICAMP)

Bachelor, Computer Engineering

UNICAMP is ranked among the top 200 universities in the world by the QS World University Rankings.